{
    "subject": "resource/Ljungby",
    "predicate": "property/source",
    "object": "SMHI Monthly Data 2002-2014",
    "human_readable": "The source of Ljungby is SMHI Monthly Data 2002-2014.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.845950722694397,
            "question": "What is the source of Ljungby data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5674344301223755,
            "question": "What type of data is provided by SMHI Monthly Data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5602895617485046,
            "question": "During what years was the data for Ljungby collected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5247315168380737,
            "question": "How often was the data collected for Ljungby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5062118172645569,
            "question": "What could be potential applications for this Ljungby data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45066896080970764,
            "question": "Is there any information about the specific measurements taken in Ljungby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4329061508178711,
            "question": "What is SMHI?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3546536862850189,
            "question": "Is there any information about the accuracy or reliability of the SMHI Monthly Data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3164735734462738,
            "question": "Where might we find more detailed information about Ljungby's climate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24969059228897095,
            "question": "Can we assume that the data includes information about the month?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The source of Ljungby is SMHI Monthly Data 2002-2014.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5193_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might we find more detailed information about Ljungby's climate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5193_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about the accuracy or reliability of the SMHI Monthly Data?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5193_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is SMHI?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5193_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5193_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided context mentions data from January 1, 1980 to December 31, 2016 as the basis for Ljungby's weather report. It doesn't specify SMHI Monthly Data 2002-2014 as the source.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention any specific data source for the weather information in Ljungby, such as SMHI Monthly Data 2002-2014. Therefore, the statement that the source of Ljungby's weather information is SMHI Monthly Data 2002-2014 cannot be supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}